William Philips

Front-End Web Developer | IT Support

https://williamphilip.github.io/ | +62 81342703275

whillys09@gmail.com

Makassar, Makassar City, South Sulawesi, Indonesia

Summary

Bachelor of engineering (Informatics) with 3 years of experience as Front-End Web Developer and 4 years of experience IT Support. Familiar with HTML, CSS and Framework CSS, SASS, modern Javascript, Library Javascript (React JS), Firebase, MongoDB and Node JS. Capable of delivering clean code based on users needs and highly adept at both independent and collaborative projects, with an emphasis on landing page and website development.

Skills

Skillset - Front-End Web Development, Problem Solving, Critical thinking, Web Design and UX/UI design, IT Support computer networks (LAN, WIFI), Installations server and computer and database server.

Toolset - React JS, Node JS, SASS/SCSS, Firebase, MongoDB, MySql, Figma, Adobe XD, Visual Studio Code, Notion.

Language

Indonesian - Native proficiency (oral and written)

English - Professional proficiency (oral and written)

Working Experience

Fronted Web Developer - Freelance

February 2024 - Present

Create and manage project website company profile tutoring reading, writing, arithmetic in Makassar (Rainbow Kids) and accommodation villas (Villa Lembah Kabut Biru) located in the city of Malino, South Sulawesi. Utilized technologies sush as Javascript, React, NodeJS, Bootstrap and MongoDB

Frontend Web Developer - Hospital Child and Mom Catherine Booth

August 2021 - February 2024

Managed multiple project website on the Front End, including the development initial design of the website project. Utilized technologies sush as React, NodeJS, Taillwind CSS, and Firebase. Consistenly met sprint deadlines, ensuring timely project delivery.

IT Support - Hospital Child and Mom Catherine Booth

July 2017 - August 2021

Maintanance of computer network, hospital information system and database. Become a trainer for hospital information systems, server installation with linux, as well as installation of the windows operating systems and repair the printer if problems occur by the user.

Education

